{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947114944675","data":{"timestamp":" 947114944675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-d-a"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947114951590","data":{"timestamp":" 947114951590"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947114956643","data":{"timestamp":" 947114956643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947114962004","data":{"timestamp":" 947114962004"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-b-d"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947114965860","data":{"timestamp":" 947114965860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947114969094","data":{"timestamp":" 947114969094"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947114983127","data":{"timestamp":" 947114983127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_o-g-j"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947114991282","data":{"timestamp":" 947114991282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-n-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947114995079","data":{"timestamp":" 947114995079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_j-l-i"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115001677","data":{"timestamp":" 947115001677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_i-l-j"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115006257","data":{"timestamp":" 947115006257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_k-f-r"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115010369","data":{"timestamp":" 947115010369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_l-j-i"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115014021","data":{"timestamp":" 947115014021"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115019012","data":{"timestamp":" 947115019012"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_u-m-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115026071","data":{"timestamp":" 947115026070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_e-o-g"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115032413","data":{"timestamp":" 947115032413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_d-b-p"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115038629","data":{"timestamp":" 947115038629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-f-r"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115046046","data":{"timestamp":" 947115046046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_l-i-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115051710","data":{"timestamp":" 947115051710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_f-r-t"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115060353","data":{"timestamp":" 947115060353"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_n-y-u"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115065676","data":{"timestamp":" 947115065676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-u-y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115069713","data":{"timestamp":" 947115069712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_m-w-n"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115073740","data":{"timestamp":" 947115073740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_y-v-u"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115077785","data":{"timestamp":" 947115077785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115083565","data":{"timestamp":" 947115083563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" b4dd935d-4a81-4e62-836d-7aa5f1e60874"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-n-m"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115111047","data":{"timestamp":" 947115111047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115111431","data":{"timestamp":" 947115111431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115111926","data":{"timestamp":" 947115111925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115112283","data":{"timestamp":" 947115112282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115112699","data":{"timestamp":" 947115112698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115113184","data":{"timestamp":" 947115113183"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115113418","data":{"timestamp":" 947115113417"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115116658","data":{"timestamp":" 947115116657"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115116699","data":{"timestamp":" 947115116699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115117426","data":{"timestamp":" 947115117425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115117830","data":{"timestamp":" 947115117829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115118134","data":{"timestamp":" 947115118134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115118350","data":{"timestamp":" 947115118349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115118555","data":{"timestamp":" 947115118555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115118883","data":{"timestamp":" 947115118882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115119121","data":{"timestamp":" 947115119121"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115122282","data":{"timestamp":" 947115122281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115122695","data":{"timestamp":" 947115122694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115125285","data":{"timestamp":" 947115125284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115125498","data":{"timestamp":" 947115125498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115125711","data":{"timestamp":" 947115125711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t u v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115129254","data":{"timestamp":" 947115129253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115133081","data":{"timestamp":" 947115133081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115134118","data":{"timestamp":" 947115134117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115136832","data":{"timestamp":" 947115136831"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115137217","data":{"timestamp":" 947115137216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115137712","data":{"timestamp":" 947115137711"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115138067","data":{"timestamp":" 947115138067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115138484","data":{"timestamp":" 947115138483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115138973","data":{"timestamp":" 947115138972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115139207","data":{"timestamp":" 947115139206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a b ch d e f g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115142386","data":{"timestamp":" 947115142385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115142425","data":{"timestamp":" 947115142425"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115143153","data":{"timestamp":" 947115143152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115143560","data":{"timestamp":" 947115143559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115143865","data":{"timestamp":" 947115143865"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115144079","data":{"timestamp":" 947115144078"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115144286","data":{"timestamp":" 947115144285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115144611","data":{"timestamp":" 947115144610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115144848","data":{"timestamp":" 947115144848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115147468","data":{"timestamp":" 947115147466"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115147592","data":{"timestamp":" 947115147592"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" 18a405c7-646f-44f6-a17e-e692e5d46eb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__abcdefg_EnglishTune_LowerCase__it_10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h i j k l m n o p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115173010","data":{"timestamp":" 947115173009"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" JASHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115182951","data":{"timestamp":" 947115182951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jasho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JASHO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115184554","data":{"timestamp":" 947115184554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115187254","data":{"timestamp":" 947115187253"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115188882","data":{"timestamp":" 947115188881"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115192192","data":{"timestamp":" 947115192192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jekundu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEKUNDU"," userResponse":" JEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115193835","data":{"timestamp":" 947115193834"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" joto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115196514","data":{"timestamp":" 947115196514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" joto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JOTO"," userResponse":" JOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115198121","data":{"timestamp":" 947115198120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115200626","data":{"timestamp":" 947115200626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jembe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JEMBE"," userResponse":" JEMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115202249","data":{"timestamp":" 947115202248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115204864","data":{"timestamp":" 947115204863"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiwe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIWE"," userResponse":" JIWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115206499","data":{"timestamp":" 947115206498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jikoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115209741","data":{"timestamp":" 947115209741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jikoni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKONI"," userResponse":" JIKONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115211329","data":{"timestamp":" 947115211328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115214099","data":{"timestamp":" 947115214099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JANI"," userResponse":" JANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115215714","data":{"timestamp":" 947115215714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jike"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKE"," userResponse":" JIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115218091","data":{"timestamp":" 947115218090"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jike"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKE"," userResponse":" JIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115219670","data":{"timestamp":" 947115219669"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115222335","data":{"timestamp":" 947115222334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115223961","data":{"timestamp":" 947115223961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115226534","data":{"timestamp":" 947115226533"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-J.rand.49","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115228565","data":{"timestamp":" 947115228564"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947115228683","data":{"timestamp":" 947115228683"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000106_022847"," gameId":" c2cc9931-ad46-4901-8a91-dd71a9329d40"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-J.rand.49"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jicho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JICHO"," userResponse":" JICHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}